Eric Martin

Colorado, United States



eric martin@me.com



linkedin.com/in/emthedm



(919) 272-2201



https://emthedm.github.io/Eric-Martin-Portfolio/

Summary

Fluent in multiple coding languages including but not limited to:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React
- SQL
- MongoDB

Have experience utilizing AGILE Methodologies while working on projects.

Created a Project Management System web app that allowed users to add client information, project asks as well as to-do's and comments so user's could work more efficiently.

Experience

Customer Support Team Lead

Gogo Business Aviation

Aug 2016 - Present (5 years 6 months +)

Partner with the Technical Support Manager in providing quality and efficient customer service.

Partner with Software Development department to perform UAT testing on new and existing projects, troubleshooting and providing feedback on new additions from that quarter's PI Planning.

Responsible for prioritizing daily workload, problem solving, training, scheduling and reward/recognition programs.

Lead the Customer Support team, ensuring high quality support. Manager of day to day operations for the teams.

Ensures continuous improvement and management of team to ensure the same high level of professionalism and quality support services for which Gogo is known.

Customer Care Engineer

Granicus

Jan 2015 - Aug 2016 (1 year 8 months)

Monitored the health of our clients' solutions using our Proactive Systems Management tools and responded to client requests within a maximum of two hours.

Maintained/modified web-based documents written in HTML/CSS & Smarty code.

Provided networking troubleshooting and provided superior customer service.

Apple Technician

Apple

Aug 2008 - Jan 2015 (6 years 6 months)

Responsible for handling repairs and replacements of Apple Products. Including but not limited to troubleshooting, diagnosis of Apple computers, and making necessary repairs according to Apple checks and procedures.

Responsible for troubleshooting various network issues including VPN settings and Outlook.

Accustom to handling a high volume of duties every day, and maintaining a high quality work product.

Continually involved in training of all Apple product knowledge and handling.

Education



University of Denver

Computer Software Engineering

2021 - 2022

Completed a Full Stack Bootcamp with the University of Denver.

UNIV University of Nevada-Las Vegas

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Film 2005 - 2012

Skills

HTML5 • JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • Web Services API • jQuery • Node.js • React.js • MongoDB • SQL

Honors & Awards



Eagle Scout Award - Boy Scouts of America

Oct 2002

I received the Eagle Scout Award at age 16.